---
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.45, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.999
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.1, find the probability of less than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 4)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)$"
    answer: 0.994
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.5, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.994
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.36, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.992
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.15, find the probability of less than 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 6)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)+P(X=4)+P(X=5)$"
    answer: 0.988
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.43, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.981
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.43, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.981
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.11, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.979
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.33, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.971
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.87, find the probability more than 13 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 13)=P(X=19)+P(X=18)+P(X=17)+P(X=16)+P(X=15)+P(X=14)$"
    answer: 0.971
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.39, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.965
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.34, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.961
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.41, find the probability of at least 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 3)=1-P(X \\lt 3) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2))$"
    answer: 0.944
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.14, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.938
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.16, find the probability of less than 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 5)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)+P(X=4)$"
    answer: 0.93
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.29, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.929
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.9, find the probability more than 13 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 13)=P(X=17)+P(X=16)+P(X=15)+P(X=14)$"
    answer: 0.917
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.87, find the probability more than 10 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 10)=P(X=14)+P(X=13)+P(X=12)+P(X=11)$"
    answer: 0.902
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.5, find the probability of at least 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 3)=1-P(X \\lt 3) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2))$"
    answer: 0.887
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.1, find the probability of less than 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 1)=P(X=0)$"
    answer: 0.886
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.15, find the probability of less than 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 3)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)$"
    answer: 0.882
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.2, find the probability of less than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 4)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)$"
    answer: 0.87
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.42, find the probability of at least 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 3)=1-P(X \\lt 3) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2))$"
    answer: 0.866
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.42, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.863
-
    question: "Given there are 15 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.27, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.814
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.86, find the probability more than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 4)=P(X=6)+P(X=5)$"
    answer: 0.8
-
    question: "Given there are 20 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.2, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.794
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.4, find the probability of at least 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 3)=1-P(X \\lt 3) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2))$"
    answer: 0.775
-
    question: "Given there are 20 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.79, find the probability more than 14 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 14)=P(X=20)+P(X=19)+P(X=18)+P(X=17)+P(X=16)+P(X=15)$"
    answer: 0.77
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.26, find the probability of at least 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 3)=1-P(X \\lt 3) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2))$"
    answer: 0.768
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.87, find the probability more than 10 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 10)=P(X=13)+P(X=12)+P(X=11)$"
    answer: 0.766
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.46, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.759
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.49, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.757
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.25, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.756
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.85, find the probability more than 13 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 13)=P(X=17)+P(X=16)+P(X=15)+P(X=14)$"
    answer: 0.756
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.86, find the probability more than 10 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 10)=P(X=13)+P(X=12)+P(X=11)$"
    answer: 0.73
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.41, find the probability of at least 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 3)=1-P(X \\lt 3) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2))$"
    answer: 0.727
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.85, find the probability more than 14 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 14)=P(X=18)+P(X=17)+P(X=16)+P(X=15)$"
    answer: 0.72
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.22, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.717
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.2, find the probability of less than 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 3)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)$"
    answer: 0.698
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.14, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.677
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.88, find the probability more than 8 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 8)=P(X=10)+P(X=9)$"
    answer: 0.658
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.77, find the probability more than 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 6)=P(X=9)+P(X=8)+P(X=7)$"
    answer: 0.657
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.33, find the probability of at least 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 5)=1-P(X \\lt 5) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)+P(X=4))$"
    answer: 0.637
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.76, find the probability more than 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 6)=P(X=9)+P(X=8)+P(X=7)$"
    answer: 0.629
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.17, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.612
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.83, find the probability more than 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 6)=P(X=8)+P(X=7)$"
    answer: 0.594
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.22, find the probability of less than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 4)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)$"
    answer: 0.59
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.23, find the probability of less than 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 1)=P(X=0)$"
    answer: 0.582
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.29, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.577
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.15, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.559
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.29, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.558
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.3, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.552
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.34, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.552
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.18, find the probability of less than 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 3)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)$"
    answer: 0.545
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.4, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.544
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.11, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.539
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.24, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.53
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.79, find the probability more than 9 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 9)=P(X=12)+P(X=11)+P(X=10)$"
    answer: 0.523
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.33, find the probability of at least 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 3)=1-P(X \\lt 3) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2))$"
    answer: 0.518
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.39, find the probability of less than 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 3)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)$"
    answer: 0.508
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.24, find the probability of less than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 4)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)$"
    answer: 0.506
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.2, find the probability of at least 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 3)=1-P(X \\lt 3) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2))$"
    answer: 0.499
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.27, find the probability of less than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 4)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)$"
    answer: 0.498
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.87, find the probability more than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 4)=P(X=5)$"
    answer: 0.498
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.77, find the probability more than 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 5)=P(X=7)+P(X=6)$"
    answer: 0.496
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.31, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.492
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.84, find the probability more than 9 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 9)=P(X=11)+P(X=10)$"
    answer: 0.455
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.23, find the probability of at least 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 4)=1-P(X \\lt 4) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3))$"
    answer: 0.452
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.3, find the probability of less than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 4)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)$"
    answer: 0.45
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.34, find the probability of less than 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 1)=P(X=0)$"
    answer: 0.448
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.85, find the probability more than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 4)=P(X=5)$"
    answer: 0.444
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.67, find the probability more than 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 12)=P(X=18)+P(X=17)+P(X=16)+P(X=15)+P(X=14)+P(X=13)$"
    answer: 0.424
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.84, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{5}C_{5}(0.84)^{5}(0.16)^{0}$"
    answer: 0.418
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.21, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.411
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.84, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{6}C_{5}(0.84)^{5}(0.16)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.401
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.76, find the probability of exactly 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=4)=^{5}C_{4}(0.76)^{4}(0.24)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.4
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.86, find the probability more than 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 12)=P(X=14)+P(X=13)$"
    answer: 0.397
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.18, find the probability of less than 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 1)=P(X=0)$"
    answer: 0.385
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.22, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.383
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.11, find the probability of exactly 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=1)=^{6}C_{1}(0.11)^{1}(0.89)^{5}$"
    answer: 0.369
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.71, find the probability of exactly 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=4)=^{5}C_{4}(0.71)^{4}(0.29)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.368
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.11, find the probability of exactly 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=1)=^{12}C_{1}(0.11)^{1}(0.89)^{11}$"
    answer: 0.366
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.11, find the probability of exactly 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=1)=^{12}C_{1}(0.11)^{1}(0.89)^{11}$"
    answer: 0.366
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.16, find the probability of less than 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 1)=P(X=0)$"
    answer: 0.36
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.69, find the probability more than 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 12)=P(X=17)+P(X=16)+P(X=15)+P(X=14)+P(X=13)$"
    answer: 0.355
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.43, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{5}C_{2}(0.43)^{2}(0.57)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.342
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.66, find the probability more than 13 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 13)=P(X=19)+P(X=18)+P(X=17)+P(X=16)+P(X=15)+P(X=14)$"
    answer: 0.329
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.33, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{5}C_{2}(0.33)^{2}(0.67)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.328
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.33, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{5}C_{2}(0.33)^{2}(0.67)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.328
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.85, find the probability of exactly 10 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=10)=^{11}C_{10}(0.85)^{10}(0.15)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.325
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.71, find the probability of exactly 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=4)=^{6}C_{4}(0.71)^{4}(0.29)^{2}$"
    answer: 0.321
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.87, find the probability of exactly 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=12)=^{13}C_{12}(0.87)^{12}(0.13)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.318
-
    question: "Given there are 15 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.19, find the probability of at least 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 3)=1-P(X \\lt 3) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2))$"
    answer: 0.315
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.14, find the probability of at least 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 1)=1-P(X \\lt 1) <br> = 1-(P(X=0))$"
    answer: 0.311
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.33, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.307
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.15, find the probability of exactly 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=1)=^{12}C_{1}(0.15)^{1}(0.85)^{11}$"
    answer: 0.301
-
    question: "Given there are 15 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.3, find the probability of less than 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 3)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)$"
    answer: 0.297
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.77, find the probability of exactly 8 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=8)=^{10}C_{8}(0.77)^{8}(0.23)^{2}$"
    answer: 0.294
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.88, find the probability of exactly 15 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=15)=^{16}C_{15}(0.88)^{15}(0.12)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.282
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.46, find the probability of less than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 4)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)$"
    answer: 0.28
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.45, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{6}C_{2}(0.45)^{2}(0.55)^{4}$"
    answer: 0.278
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.21, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{12}C_{2}(0.21)^{2}(0.79)^{10}$"
    answer: 0.276
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.77, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{5}C_{5}(0.77)^{5}(0.23)^{0}$"
    answer: 0.271
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.17, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{7}C_{0}(0.17)^{0}(0.83)^{7}$"
    answer: 0.271
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.46, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{6}C_{2}(0.46)^{2}(0.54)^{4}$"
    answer: 0.27
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.43, find the probability of exactly 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=3)=^{8}C_{3}(0.43)^{3}(0.57)^{5}$"
    answer: 0.268
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.76, find the probability of exactly 9 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=9)=^{11}C_{9}(0.76)^{9}(0.24)^{2}$"
    answer: 0.268
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.1, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.266
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.2, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.262
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.75, find the probability of exactly 8 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=8)=^{11}C_{8}(0.75)^{8}(0.25)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.258
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.55, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{8}C_{5}(0.55)^{5}(0.45)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.257
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.48, find the probability of exactly 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=4)=^{9}C_{4}(0.48)^{4}(0.52)^{5}$"
    answer: 0.254
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.29, find the probability of at least 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 3)=1-P(X \\lt 3) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2))$"
    answer: 0.248
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.84, find the probability more than 7 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 7)=P(X=8)$"
    answer: 0.248
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.59, find the probability of exactly 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=4)=^{5}C_{4}(0.59)^{4}(0.41)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.248
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.19, find the probability of exactly 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=3)=^{14}C_{3}(0.19)^{3}(0.81)^{11}$"
    answer: 0.246
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.83, find the probability of exactly 15 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=15)=^{18}C_{15}(0.83)^{15}(0.17)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.245
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.76, find the probability of exactly 10 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=10)=^{12}C_{10}(0.76)^{10}(0.24)^{2}$"
    answer: 0.244
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.56, find the probability of exactly 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=6)=^{10}C_{6}(0.56)^{6}(0.44)^{4}$"
    answer: 0.243
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.56, find the probability of exactly 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=6)=^{10}C_{6}(0.56)^{6}(0.44)^{4}$"
    answer: 0.243
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.63, find the probability of exactly 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=6)=^{8}C_{6}(0.63)^{6}(0.37)^{2}$"
    answer: 0.24
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.45, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{11}C_{5}(0.45)^{5}(0.55)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.236
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.52, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{8}C_{5}(0.52)^{5}(0.48)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.235
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.69, find the probability of exactly 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=6)=^{7}C_{6}(0.69)^{6}(0.31)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.234
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.1, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{12}C_{2}(0.1)^{2}(0.9)^{10}$"
    answer: 0.23
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.81, find the probability more than 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 6)=P(X=7)$"
    answer: 0.229
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.47, find the probability of less than 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 1)=P(X=0)$"
    answer: 0.227
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.23, find the probability of exactly 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=4)=^{17}C_{4}(0.23)^{4}(0.77)^{13}$"
    answer: 0.223
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.68, find the probability of exactly 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=6)=^{7}C_{6}(0.68)^{6}(0.32)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.221
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.87, find the probability of exactly 17 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=17)=^{18}C_{17}(0.87)^{17}(0.13)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.219
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.77, find the probability of exactly 9 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=9)=^{10}C_{9}(0.77)^{9}(0.23)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.219
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.9, find the probability of exactly 9 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=9)=^{11}C_{9}(0.9)^{9}(0.1)^{2}$"
    answer: 0.213
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.29, find the probability of exactly 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=1)=^{8}C_{1}(0.29)^{1}(0.71)^{7}$"
    answer: 0.211
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.56, find the probability of exactly 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=6)=^{12}C_{6}(0.56)^{6}(0.44)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.207
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.61, find the probability of exactly 8 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=8)=^{14}C_{8}(0.61)^{8}(0.39)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.203
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.3, find the probability of exactly 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=4)=^{10}C_{4}(0.3)^{4}(0.7)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.2
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.85, find the probability more than 17 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 17)=P(X=19)+P(X=18)$"
    answer: 0.198
-
    question: "Given there are 15 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.44, find the probability of exactly 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=6)=^{15}C_{6}(0.44)^{6}(0.56)^{9}$"
    answer: 0.197
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.34, find the probability of exactly 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=6)=^{18}C_{6}(0.34)^{6}(0.66)^{12}$"
    answer: 0.196
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.86, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{7}C_{5}(0.86)^{5}(0.14)^{2}$"
    answer: 0.194
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.19, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{5}C_{2}(0.19)^{2}(0.81)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.192
-
    question: "Given there are 15 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.35, find the probability of exactly 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=6)=^{15}C_{6}(0.35)^{6}(0.65)^{9}$"
    answer: 0.191
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.81, find the probability of exactly 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=12)=^{16}C_{12}(0.81)^{12}(0.19)^{4}$"
    answer: 0.189
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.69, find the probability of exactly 8 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=8)=^{13}C_{8}(0.69)^{8}(0.31)^{5}$"
    answer: 0.189
-
    question: "Given there are 15 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.17, find the probability of exactly 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=1)=^{15}C_{1}(0.17)^{1}(0.83)^{14}$"
    answer: 0.188
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.48, find the probability of exactly 7 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=7)=^{16}C_{7}(0.48)^{7}(0.52)^{9}$"
    answer: 0.187
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.84, find the probability of exactly 15 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=15)=^{19}C_{15}(0.84)^{15}(0.16)^{4}$"
    answer: 0.186
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.35, find the probability of exactly 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=1)=^{7}C_{1}(0.35)^{1}(0.65)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.185
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.7, find the probability of exactly 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=3)=^{6}C_{3}(0.7)^{3}(0.3)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.185
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.5, find the probability of exactly 8 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=8)=^{17}C_{8}(0.5)^{8}(0.5)^{9}$"
    answer: 0.185
-
    question: "Given there are 20 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.21, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{20}C_{5}(0.21)^{5}(0.79)^{15}$"
    answer: 0.184
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.43, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{8}C_{2}(0.43)^{2}(0.57)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.178
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.15, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{6}C_{2}(0.15)^{2}(0.85)^{4}$"
    answer: 0.176
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.57, find the probability of exactly 11 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=11)=^{17}C_{11}(0.57)^{11}(0.43)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.161
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.79, find the probability of exactly 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=12)=^{13}C_{12}(0.79)^{12}(0.21)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.161
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.33, find the probability of exactly 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=1)=^{8}C_{1}(0.33)^{1}(0.67)^{7}$"
    answer: 0.16
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.28, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{13}C_{5}(0.28)^{5}(0.72)^{8}$"
    answer: 0.16
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.76, find the probability of exactly 7 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=7)=^{11}C_{7}(0.76)^{7}(0.24)^{4}$"
    answer: 0.16
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.12, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{7}C_{2}(0.12)^{2}(0.88)^{5}$"
    answer: 0.16
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.34, find the probability of less than 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 3)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)$"
    answer: 0.153
-
    question: "Given there are 20 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.22, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.151
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.46, find the probability of less than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 4)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)$"
    answer: 0.149
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.18, find the probability of at least 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 4)=1-P(X \\lt 4) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3))$"
    answer: 0.146
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.53, find the probability of exactly 7 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=7)=^{10}C_{7}(0.53)^{7}(0.47)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.146
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.74, find the probability of exactly 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=3)=^{6}C_{3}(0.74)^{3}(0.26)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.142
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.72, find the probability of exactly 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=6)=^{6}C_{6}(0.72)^{6}(0.28)^{0}$"
    answer: 0.139
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.46, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.136
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.33, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{5}C_{0}(0.33)^{0}(0.67)^{5}$"
    answer: 0.135
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.73, find the probability of exactly 10 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=10)=^{16}C_{10}(0.73)^{10}(0.27)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.133
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.47, find the probability of less than 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 6)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)+P(X=4)+P(X=5)$"
    answer: 0.132
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.2, find the probability of at least 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 4)=1-P(X \\lt 4) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3))$"
    answer: 0.13
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.38, find the probability of exactly 9 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=9)=^{19}C_{9}(0.38)^{9}(0.62)^{10}$"
    answer: 0.128
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.45, find the probability of exactly 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=3)=^{11}C_{3}(0.45)^{3}(0.55)^{8}$"
    answer: 0.126
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.16, find the probability of exactly 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=3)=^{9}C_{3}(0.16)^{3}(0.84)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.121
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.37, find the probability of exactly 9 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=9)=^{19}C_{9}(0.37)^{9}(0.63)^{10}$"
    answer: 0.118
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.53, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{6}C_{5}(0.53)^{5}(0.47)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.118
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.64, find the probability of exactly 7 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=7)=^{14}C_{7}(0.64)^{7}(0.36)^{7}$"
    answer: 0.118
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.5, find the probability of exactly 7 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=7)=^{10}C_{7}(0.5)^{7}(0.5)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.117
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.24, find the probability of less than 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 1)=P(X=0)$"
    answer: 0.116
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.71, find the probability more than 13 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 13)=P(X=16)+P(X=15)+P(X=14)$"
    answer: 0.115
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.52, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{6}C_{5}(0.52)^{5}(0.48)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.109
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.83, find the probability of exactly 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=12)=^{12}C_{12}(0.83)^{12}(0.17)^{0}$"
    answer: 0.107
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.83, find the probability more than 11 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 11)=P(X=12)$"
    answer: 0.107
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.4, find the probability of less than 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 1)=P(X=0)$"
    answer: 0.106
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.62, find the probability of exactly 11 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=11)=^{14}C_{11}(0.62)^{11}(0.38)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.104
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.49, find the probability of less than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 4)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)$"
    answer: 0.103
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.22, find the probability of at least 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 4)=1-P(X \\lt 4) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3))$"
    answer: 0.102
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.64, find the probability of exactly 10 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=10)=^{12}C_{10}(0.64)^{10}(0.36)^{2}$"
    answer: 0.099
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.71, find the probability more than 10 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 10)=P(X=12)+P(X=11)$"
    answer: 0.097
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.26, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.094
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.74, find the probability more than 16 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 16)=P(X=19)+P(X=18)+P(X=17)$"
    answer: 0.094
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.26, find the probability of exactly 7 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=7)=^{18}C_{7}(0.26)^{7}(0.74)^{11}$"
    answer: 0.093
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.26, find the probability of exactly 7 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=7)=^{18}C_{7}(0.26)^{7}(0.74)^{11}$"
    answer: 0.093
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.5, find the probability of less than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 4)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)$"
    answer: 0.09
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.13, find the probability of at least 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 4)=1-P(X \\lt 4) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3))$"
    answer: 0.09
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.49, find the probability of exactly 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=3)=^{11}C_{3}(0.49)^{3}(0.51)^{8}$"
    answer: 0.089
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.4, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{11}C_{2}(0.4)^{2}(0.6)^{9}$"
    answer: 0.089
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.74, find the probability more than 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 12)=P(X=14)+P(X=13)$"
    answer: 0.087
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.35, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.084
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.57, find the probability of exactly 13 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=13)=^{18}C_{13}(0.57)^{13}(0.43)^{5}$"
    answer: 0.084
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.13, find the probability of exactly 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=3)=^{9}C_{3}(0.13)^{3}(0.87)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.08
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.75, find the probability more than 8 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 8)=P(X=9)$"
    answer: 0.075
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.17, find the probability of at least 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 3)=1-P(X \\lt 3) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2))$"
    answer: 0.074
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.77, find the probability more than 9 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 9)=P(X=10)$"
    answer: 0.073
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.72, find the probability of exactly 8 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=8)=^{8}C_{8}(0.72)^{8}(0.28)^{0}$"
    answer: 0.072
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.44, find the probability of less than 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 1)=P(X=0)$"
    answer: 0.07
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.61, find the probability of exactly 14 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=14)=^{18}C_{14}(0.61)^{14}(0.39)^{4}$"
    answer: 0.07
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.51, find the probability more than 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 5)=P(X=7)+P(X=6)$"
    answer: 0.069
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.18, find the probability of at least 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 4)=1-P(X \\lt 4) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3))$"
    answer: 0.068
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.15, find the probability of exactly 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=4)=^{12}C_{4}(0.15)^{4}(0.85)^{8}$"
    answer: 0.068
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.84, find the probability of exactly 11 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=11)=^{16}C_{11}(0.84)^{11}(0.16)^{5}$"
    answer: 0.067
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.67, find the probability of exactly 10 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=10)=^{11}C_{10}(0.67)^{10}(0.33)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.066
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.13, find the probability of exactly 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=3)=^{8}C_{3}(0.13)^{3}(0.87)^{5}$"
    answer: 0.061
-
    question: "Given there are 5 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.57, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{5}C_{5}(0.57)^{5}(0.43)^{0}$"
    answer: 0.06
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.16, find the probability of at least 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 4)=1-P(X \\lt 4) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3))$"
    answer: 0.059
-
    question: "Given there are 20 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.71, find the probability of exactly 11 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=11)=^{20}C_{11}(0.71)^{11}(0.29)^{9}$"
    answer: 0.056
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.77, find the probability of exactly 11 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=11)=^{11}C_{11}(0.77)^{11}(0.23)^{0}$"
    answer: 0.056
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.83, find the probability of exactly 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=3)=^{6}C_{3}(0.83)^{3}(0.17)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.056
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.15, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{18}C_{0}(0.15)^{0}(0.85)^{18}$"
    answer: 0.054
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.83, find the probability more than 15 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 15)=P(X=16)$"
    answer: 0.051
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.46, find the probability of less than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 4)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)$"
    answer: 0.05
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.47, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.05
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.18, find the probability of exactly 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=5)=^{13}C_{5}(0.18)^{5}(0.82)^{8}$"
    answer: 0.05
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.5, find the probability more than 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 12)=P(X=18)+P(X=17)+P(X=16)+P(X=15)+P(X=14)+P(X=13)$"
    answer: 0.048
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.48, find the probability of less than 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 1)=P(X=0)$"
    answer: 0.045
-
    question: "Given there are 20 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.77, find the probability of exactly 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=12)=^{20}C_{12}(0.77)^{12}(0.23)^{8}$"
    answer: 0.043
-
    question: "Given there are 15 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.5, find the probability of exactly 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=4)=^{15}C_{4}(0.5)^{4}(0.5)^{11}$"
    answer: 0.042
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.45, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.042
-
    question: "Given there are 15 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.45, find the probability of less than 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 3)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)$"
    answer: 0.042
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.59, find the probability more than 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 5)=P(X=6)$"
    answer: 0.042
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.59, find the probability more than 8 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 8)=P(X=10)+P(X=9)$"
    answer: 0.041
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.79, find the probability more than 13 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 13)=P(X=14)$"
    answer: 0.037
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.59, find the probability of exactly 9 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=9)=^{10}C_{9}(0.59)^{9}(0.41)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.036
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.66, find the probability of exactly 8 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=8)=^{8}C_{8}(0.66)^{8}(0.34)^{0}$"
    answer: 0.036
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.55, find the probability of exactly 10 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=10)=^{12}C_{10}(0.55)^{10}(0.45)^{2}$"
    answer: 0.034
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.77, find the probability more than 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 12)=P(X=13)$"
    answer: 0.033
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.29, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{10}C_{0}(0.29)^{0}(0.71)^{10}$"
    answer: 0.033
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.25, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{12}C_{0}(0.25)^{0}(0.75)^{12}$"
    answer: 0.032
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.75, find the probability more than 11 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 11)=P(X=12)$"
    answer: 0.032
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.5, find the probability of exactly 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=1)=^{8}C_{1}(0.5)^{1}(0.5)^{7}$"
    answer: 0.031
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.68, find the probability more than 8 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 8)=P(X=9)$"
    answer: 0.031
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.18, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{18}C_{0}(0.18)^{0}(0.82)^{18}$"
    answer: 0.028
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.43, find the probability of less than 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 3)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)$"
    answer: 0.027
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.1, find the probability of at least 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 2)=1-P(X \\lt 2) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1))$"
    answer: 0.026
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.51, find the probability of exactly 11 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=11)=^{14}C_{11}(0.51)^{11}(0.49)^{3}$"
    answer: 0.026
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.12, find the probability of at least 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 3)=1-P(X \\lt 3) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2))$"
    answer: 0.024
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.15, find the probability of exactly 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=6)=^{17}C_{6}(0.15)^{6}(0.85)^{11}$"
    answer: 0.024
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.4, find the probability of less than 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 3)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)$"
    answer: 0.023
-
    question: "Given there are 20 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.24, find the probability of exactly 9 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=9)=^{20}C_{9}(0.24)^{9}(0.76)^{11}$"
    answer: 0.022
-
    question: "Given there are 10 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.32, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{10}C_{0}(0.32)^{0}(0.68)^{10}$"
    answer: 0.021
-
    question: "Given there are 6 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.48, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{6}C_{0}(0.48)^{0}(0.52)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.02
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.59, find the probability more than 15 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 15)=P(X=19)+P(X=18)+P(X=17)+P(X=16)$"
    answer: 0.019
-
    question: "Given there are 13 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.63, find the probability of exactly 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=12)=^{13}C_{12}(0.63)^{12}(0.37)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.019
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.36, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{9}C_{0}(0.36)^{0}(0.64)^{9}$"
    answer: 0.018
-
    question: "Given there are 15 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.33, find the probability of exactly 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=1)=^{15}C_{1}(0.33)^{1}(0.67)^{14}$"
    answer: 0.018
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.71, find the probability more than 11 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 11)=P(X=12)$"
    answer: 0.016
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.48, find the probability of less than 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 4)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)$"
    answer: 0.015
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.59, find the probability more than 7 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 7)=P(X=8)$"
    answer: 0.015
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.59, find the probability more than 7 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 7)=P(X=8)$"
    answer: 0.015
-
    question: "Given there are 15 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.89, find the probability of exactly 10 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=10)=^{15}C_{10}(0.89)^{10}(0.11)^{5}$"
    answer: 0.015
-
    question: "Given there are 15 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.5, find the probability of exactly 3 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=3)=^{15}C_{3}(0.5)^{3}(0.5)^{12}$"
    answer: 0.014
-
    question: "Given there are 11 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.32, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{11}C_{0}(0.32)^{0}(0.68)^{11}$"
    answer: 0.014
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.42, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{8}C_{0}(0.42)^{0}(0.58)^{8}$"
    answer: 0.013
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.46, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{7}C_{0}(0.46)^{0}(0.54)^{7}$"
    answer: 0.013
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.47, find the probability of less than 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 2)=P(X=0)+P(X=1)$"
    answer: 0.012
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.53, find the probability more than 6 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 6)=P(X=7)$"
    answer: 0.012
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.88, find the probability of exactly 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=12)=^{18}C_{12}(0.88)^{12}(0.12)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.012
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.57, find the probability of exactly 11 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=11)=^{12}C_{11}(0.57)^{11}(0.43)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.011
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.12, find the probability of at least 5 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\ge 5)=1-P(X \\lt 5) <br> = 1-(P(X=0)+P(X=1)+P(X=2)+P(X=3)+P(X=4))$"
    answer: 0.011
-
    question: "Given there are 20 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.46, find the probability of exactly 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=4)=^{20}C_{4}(0.46)^{4}(0.54)^{16}$"
    answer: 0.011
-
    question: "Given there are 7 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.52, find the probability of exactly 7 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=7)=^{7}C_{7}(0.52)^{7}(0.48)^{0}$"
    answer: 0.01
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.89, find the probability of exactly 12 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=12)=^{18}C_{12}(0.89)^{12}(0.11)^{6}$"
    answer: 0.008
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.35, find the probability of less than 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 1)=P(X=0)$"
    answer: 0.007
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.65, find the probability more than 15 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 15)=P(X=17)+P(X=16)$"
    answer: 0.007
-
    question: "Given there are 9 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.1, find the probability of exactly 4 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=4)=^{9}C_{4}(0.1)^{4}(0.9)^{5}$"
    answer: 0.007
-
    question: "Given there are 15 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.83, find the probability of exactly 8 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=8)=^{15}C_{8}(0.83)^{8}(0.17)^{7}$"
    answer: 0.006
-
    question: "Given there are 8 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.47, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{8}C_{0}(0.47)^{0}(0.53)^{8}$"
    answer: 0.006
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.73, find the probability of exactly 17 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=17)=^{17}C_{17}(0.73)^{17}(0.27)^{0}$"
    answer: 0.005
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.53, find the probability of exactly 14 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=14)=^{16}C_{14}(0.53)^{14}(0.47)^{2}$"
    answer: 0.004
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.34, find the probability of exactly 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=1)=^{19}C_{1}(0.34)^{1}(0.66)^{18}$"
    answer: 0.004
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.48, find the probability of exactly 2 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=2)=^{16}C_{2}(0.48)^{2}(0.52)^{14}$"
    answer: 0.003
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.57, find the probability more than 16 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 16)=P(X=19)+P(X=18)+P(X=17)$"
    answer: 0.003
-
    question: "Given there are 17 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.53, find the probability more than 14 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\gt 14)=P(X=17)+P(X=16)+P(X=15)$"
    answer: 0.003
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.58, find the probability of exactly 17 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=17)=^{19}C_{17}(0.58)^{17}(0.42)^{2}$"
    answer: 0.003
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.5, find the probability of exactly 11 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=11)=^{12}C_{11}(0.5)^{11}(0.5)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.003
-
    question: "Given there are 18 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.81, find the probability of exactly 9 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=9)=^{18}C_{9}(0.81)^{9}(0.19)^{9}$"
    answer: 0.002
-
    question: "Given there are 14 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.65, find the probability of exactly 14 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=14)=^{14}C_{14}(0.65)^{14}(0.35)^{0}$"
    answer: 0.002
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.46, find the probability of less than 1 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X \\lt 1)=P(X=0)$"
    answer: 0.001
-
    question: "Given there are 19 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.54, find the probability of exactly 17 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=17)=^{19}C_{17}(0.54)^{17}(0.46)^{2}$"
    answer: 0.001
-
    question: "Given there are 12 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.43, find the probability of exactly 0 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=0)=^{12}C_{0}(0.43)^{0}(0.57)^{12}$"
    answer: 0.001
-
    question: "Given there are 16 independent trials, each with probability of success of 0.53, find the probability of exactly 15 successes. Give answers to 3 decimal places"
    solution: "$P(X=x)=^{n}C_{x} p^{x} (1-p)^{n-x}$ <br><br> $P(X=15)=^{16}C_{15}(0.53)^{15}(0.47)^{1}$"
    answer: 0.001
